[MARIELA] Your life is so good!
But my daughter…
She just asked for help.
She made some small mistakes.
Don't you have a heart?
You have no empathy!
Not even a little bit.
[BEA] Let me deal with Billy.
I'll handle her.
I can do that.
Mmm, want more?
- [PETER] Yeah.
- [BEA] Hmm, yes?
- Yes, sure.
- Yes? Okay.
- Game.
- I'll take care of it. [CHUCKLES]
You're the boss.
- Wait for me.
- Mm-hmm.
[BEA LAUGHS SHORTLY]
Here we go.
[PETER SLURRING] Yes, baby.
[BEA] Here.
[PETER] Here we go.
Bottoms up!
- Mm-hmm.
- [PETER CHUCKLING]
Oh.
[BEA] It's good, right?
Now…
[PETER] Now…
[CHUCKLES]
- [BEA] Are you ready?
- [PETER] Yes, I am.
Why are you so beautiful?
[BEA] You're just a lightweight.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHUTTER CLICKING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Robbie.
Oh, Val.
No hard feelings, okay?
Absolutely.
No hard feelings, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
[JORDAN] Come on.
Why don't you give him a chance?
I can ask you the same thing.
What do you mean?
You wrote this, right?
Yeah.
- But…
- I knew it.
But what's written there is true.
Yeah.
But you didn't write this
to express Robbie's feelings for me.
You wrote it to express your feelings
for someone else.
[PRECIOUS] I secretly recorded this too,
so I could show it to you.
Here.
Your father said
he'll never leave you guys again.
Have you made your decision, Billy?
I gave Oliver what he wanted.
But that's it.
This is going to hurt him.
Is it just Oliver who will get hurt?
Or you too?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN] What the hell?!
The road is so wide!
Stop blocking the way!
- I'm just over here on the side!
- Ugh! Don't you have eyes?!
- Idiot! Just get out of here!
- You're unbelievable!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARIELA SCREAMING]
- [MARIELA SCREAMING]
- M-Ma?
Ma.
Ma?
I'm here, Ma.
You're having a bad dream.
Wake up.
Are you okay?
- Hm?
- As long as your father
and his mistress are together
with that Billy and her little brother,
those bastard children…
I will never be okay.
Never.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Drink this first.
- [BEA] Here. Go on, Ma.
- [SOFT RUSTLING]
Drink it.
[SOFT RUSTLING]
Ma.
[SOFT THUD]
I told you, didn't I?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll deal with them.
I'm working on it.
Especially with Billy.
Mark my words. Billy is going down.
So don't think about it anymore.
Don't worry about Billy
or any of them anymore.
I'm working on it. Okay, Ma?
Leave everything to me.
You hear me?
Now…
You need to get up now, Ma.
Get up because…
Look at what I ordered!
We've got so much food!
We've got grapes and cupcakes!
And…
You don't really eat salad,
but let's try it because it looks good.
And-- Is that pork chop or steak?
I've got you some chicken too.
And I skipped the coffee this time
and ordered red wine instead.
Hmm?
Come on and eat, Ma.
[BEA] So, what do you want to eat first?
- [SOFT THUD]
- Oh.
Look, Ma.
See?
It's still early, but…
Mmm! I got you some red wine.
You like that, right?
Well, what do you want?
Pork chop? Or is this steak?
There's chicken too!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, please. I need more time with him.
It's already more than enough that
you were given the chance
to spend time with Oliver.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If we're being honest, I shouldn't have
allowed it in the first place.
If you're afraid that the person who was
after me will bother you,
that won't happen.
He's been locked up.
He's scammed a lot of people.
[BILLY] I know my brother will be hurt
when he finds out that I stopped you
from seeing him.
But it's better this way
than to drag this out.
I'll give you one week.
Please, don't hurt my brother anymore.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I super like my room.
It's so huge. Wow!
I slept so well. I feel so relaxed.
Thank you so much, Peter.
But, you know,
I feel like our rooms
should be next to each other.
So, you know…
I can keep an eye on you
in case you bring a woman over.
I'll tell your wife about it.
I won't bring anyone, okay?
Okay, relax.
Inhale, exhale, Peter.
Just…
do what I asked, okay?
Hack into LoveLine ASAP.
- Clear?
- Yes.
I'm working on it.
You better be.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Because if you don't do it,
your photos will go viral.
I'm telling you.
And when they do…
Oh no! You'll lose your license.
Then…
[BEA GASPS]
your family will disown you.
And your wife?
You'll end up getting a divorce.
We don't want that, do we, Peter?
Do we?
So you'll do what I asked, okay?
Can I hear you say, "Okay, Bea"?
- Okay, Bea.
- Okay.
All right, go on.
Go to LoveList. Hack it now.
Right now.
Thank you!
Take care--Oh!
I'll order some food.
Thank you!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BLAIRE] Oh, hi, Sir Fab! What a surprise!
- Uh, do you want coffee?
- [UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Tea? Juice? Glutinous rice balls
in coconut milk?
Uh, I'd like to take a look at
the LoveLine area.
May I?
Um, it's confidential.
But you can take a look at me instead.
But I'm an investor, so… may I?
- May you?
- Yeah.
Y-Yes, you may.
Please enter.
Feel at home.
Yeah, yeah. [CHUCKLES]
You have a lot of hardworking agents here.
He said we're hardworking!
Good work, guys!
So, does every agent have
their own login credentials,
or do they all share accounts
during their shifts?
Uh… um…
- They have their own login, sir.
- Right.
So, you must be
changing passwords often, then.
- Right?
- Um…
- Maybe?
- [CLEARS THROAT]
So, I mean, what happens if an agent
forgets their password?
How do they reset it?
Uh… reset?
- Yeah, how do they reset?
- Reset?
Um… They…
They… They click "reset password," sir.
Yes, they click "reset password."
Right.
Do you run an intrusion detection program
on your network?
In-In-Intrusion?
Yeah, intrusion detection program.
Intrusion?
I-I don't know if…
Maybe extension.
I…
[BLAIRE BREATHING HEAVILY]
Are you okay?
No, I'm Blaire. I'm not "Okay," sir.
Uh, wait a minute.
Um, I-I'll ask Chief Billy, okay?
- Yeah.
- Y-You stay here.
You wait. You…
- Stay there.
- Okay, okay. I will.
[BLAIRE MUTTERING] Intrusion? Huh?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BUILDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sorry, chief. Sir Peter's here.
Huh? You didn't tell me
he was coming today.
He just suddenly arrived.
I thought you were expecting him.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Then he started asking me
all sorts of techy questions.
Huh? What is he asking?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hi!
- Peter!
- Hi!
Sorry, I wasn't expecting you.
Hi. Yeah…
[STUTTERING] I was just looking around.
Oh, okay. Do you have
any questions or concerns?
I can arrange a meeting right now.
No, no. No need for that.
I, uh…
Actually, I was wondering about one thing.
- Okay.
- The data.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is it, you know…
automatically encrypted
as the phone calls happen,
or is it encrypted after?
After. Of course.
Right. Of course. Yes, yes. Uhm…
I guess that's it then. Yeah.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you want a more extensive tour
or if you have questions
on our operations…
No, no, no. I don't think
that would be necessary.
- Okay.
- I was really just on my way out, so.
I'll schedule another meeting
within the week.
- Yes? Okay.
- Yes, of course. Anytime.
All right.
Blaire, please see him on his way out.
- Okay, chief.
- Ah, no, no, no.
That won't be necessary. I got this.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
I know where the exit is.
Thank you. [LAUGHS]
- See you.
- [PETER] Yeah, see you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[KNOCKING ON THE DOOR]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh! Peter!
[GASPS] You already hacked it?
You're fast!
Now, I expect you to fulfill
your end of the deal.
Delete those photos.
Mm.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Of course, I have to check this first.
I have to double-check,
or even triple-check,
if everything I need is in here.
You think I would risk
everything for a fake?
You have no idea what I had to
go through just to get those!
Mm… Is that so?
Okay. I don't care.
Come on!
You know, Peter,
our deal was simple.
Once LoveList is completely ruined,
that's when I'll delete all the pictures.
Okay?
- Bye!
- Wait.
That's not what you said.
Yes. I know.
So now, I'm telling you.
Okay, you can go now. I'll check this.
Thank you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES CONTENTEDLY]
Hmm.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CALLER 1] I think my
boyfriend is cheating.
I checked his phone.
He's flirting with Rio dela Cuesta.
The celebrity endorser-slash-model.
[CALLER 2] Gio Baldemor
sent me a nude picture.
The one I matched with here in LoveList.
Now, he wants me to do the same!
Is that right?
[CALLER 3] I lied to my boyfriend
about my background.
I didn't tell him I have a child
from a previous relationship.
What do I do?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What's this?
What's happening?
What is this?
[LAPTOP SLAMMING SHUT]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
This is the big news, chief.
Ever since we announced
that LoveList is going global,
there has been a huge spike
in the number of subscribers,
and the increase in membership
sign-ups has been consistent.
- Hmm.
- Another thing, girls.
We've been receiving lots of inquiries
about ad placement on the platform!
- Wow!
- [BILLY] Good job!
- [CLAPPING]
- Good job!
Great! Finally!
- Thank you, Morrie!
- [TONI] Congrats!
- [VALERIE] Billy? We have a problem.
- [BILLY] Yes?
Someone posted this,
and it's gaining traction.
"Your secret's not safe with LoveList!"
"Confidential LoveLine conversation
and member information leaked!"
Why does the message say that?
What's going on?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello?
Jordan.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[EMPLOYEE] Your data is secure with us.
Yup. Someone definitely tried
to leak the files.
Tough luck for them,
all of our confidential data is encrypted.
And we have a second layer of protection,
so if anyone tries to hack,
leak our files,
this will pop up.
[EXHALES] Okay, good.
But, dude, how did they get our data?
Good thing you went ahead
with the security measures.
Well, you hired
a great cybersecurity group.
So, your investment paid off.
Besides, you were the one
who reminded me, right?
To protect our secrets.
I'm curious how they slipped
under our noses.
I checked with security,
and no one got in that we didn't know.
Do you think it was Bea again?
Caloy is in prison, isn't he?
So who would she send this time
to gain access to our computers?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, chief. Sir Peter's here.
Huh? Why are you only telling me now?
He just suddenly arrived.
I thought you were expecting him.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hi! Peter!
- Hi!
Sorry, I wasn't expecting you.
Hi. Yeah.
[STUTTERING] I was just looking around.
Oh, okay. Do you have
any questions or concerns?
I can arrange a meeting right now.
No, no. No need for that.
I, uh…
Actually, I was wondering about one thing.
- Okay.
- The data.
Is it, you know,
automatically encrypted
as the phone calls happen,
or is it encrypted after?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But one of our other suspects
is our investor.
But I'm wondering,
why would he want
to ruin LoveList
when he invested
in it himself?
You should ask the police for help.
- Your files are corrupted!
- No, it's encrypted.
[BEA] Are you going to hit me?
Go! Go ahead! Hit me.
I'm trying to trace the activity
on the workstation
where Peter was sitting.
[BILLY] See you tomorrow, dude.
Thank you.
[MARIELA]
They're living lavishly.
They have a beautiful house.
They're living a luxurious life.
[SOBS] And now,
they have your father too!
And what do we have?
Nothing!
[BEA] Ma?
Marj found out that
Peter is staying here.
So, wait. You think it's really him?
[BILLY] Dude,
he invested 30 million in us.
It makes no sense if he actually
wants the company to fail.